<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>Matheus Leonel Balduino Blog</title>
        <link>https://mathbalduino.com.br/blog</link>
        <description>Matheus Leonel Balduino Blog</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Beginning]]></title>
            <link>https://mathbalduino.com.br/blog/the-beginning</link>
            <guid>the-beginning</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[So, this year I decided to start exposing the work I've been doing over the last few years, to the internet. Hope you like]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>So, this year I decided to start exposing the work I've been doing over the last few years, to the internet. Hope you like
it! This decision came after a relatively long period of isolation (hello pandemic!), and because I thought that this could be
a very interesting way to show the world what I can really do. Yes, it's a little stressful for me when I'm showing a
authoring work, but let me test myself!</p><p>From now on, I will use my social media networks and this site who speaks to you to showcase my authorship works (usually,
under the index page). In addition, I'll be writing blog posts to talk about the decisions I made on my projects,
some guides explaining how I achieved the results I got, programming tutorials and some opinion posts about things
of my interest (usually about software development or tech-related stuff).</p><p>As you may have noticed, I'm not a native English speaker (surprise, surprise!). This blog will be a great opportunity to
improve my english too, so if you notice any errors (of any kind), please let me know.</p><p>In the coming weeks, I'll be posting about how I made the infrastructure of my personal website, and project websites,
in more detail (GitHub Pages, Custom domains and Docusaurus, basically).</p><p>See you soon!</p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>